Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪I plant miles of peach blossoms just for her♪
أزرع أميالاً من أزهار الخوخ خصيصاً من أجلها
♪Sweet words bloom upon those branches♪
♪تزهر الكلمات العذبة على تلك الأغصان♪
♪Love runs deep, trapped in longing♪
♪الحب عميق، محاصر في الشوق♪
♪Night listens answers to longing are the most terrifying♪
♪تستمع الليل إلى إجابات الشوق، وهي الأكثر رعباً♪
♪At my fingertips, worries drift and linger♪
♪على أطراف أصابعي، تتلاشى الهموم وتستمر♪
♪Having tasted a moment of carefree joy♪
♪ بعد أن تذوقت لحظة من الفرح الخالي من الهموم ♪
♪Today, I pluck romance and moonlight♪
اليوم، أقطف الرومانسية وضوء القمر
♪And weave them all into a painting♪
♪ واجمعها كلها في لوحة ♪
=The Ultimate Vow, Unknown to You=
=العهد الأسمى، الذي تجهله=
=Episode 8=
=الحلقة 8=
Little beauty.
جمال صغير.
Let's have some fun today.
لنستمتع قليلاً اليوم.
Don't come near.
لا تقترب.
Stay back!
ابتعدوا!
(Chengguang Hall)
(قاعة تشنغ قوانغ)
Sir Heng Dao.
السير هنغ داو.
Is His Highness here?
هل صاحب السمو هنا؟
He left the palace on business.
غادر القصر في مهمة عمل.
Not back yet.
لم أعد بعد.
This...
هذا...
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Has something happened?
هل حدث شيء ما؟
Well.
حسنًا.
Miss Shen is in prison.
الآنسة شين في السجن.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
I passed by it just now.
مررت من هناك للتو.
I heard
سمعت
strange screams from a woman inside.
صرخات غريبة تصدر من امرأة في الداخل.
This could damage His Highness's reputation.
قد يؤدي هذا إلى الإضرار بسمعة صاحب السمو.
If word gets out...
إذا انتشر الخبر...
Lead the way.
كن رائداً.
His Highness cares deeply for her,
صاحب السمو يكن لها محبة عميقة،
yet she...
لكنها...
Your Ladyship.
سيدتي.
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I only did it to protect His Highness's reputation.
لم أفعل ذلك إلا لحماية سمعة صاحب السمو.
If it weren't urgent,
لو لم يكن الأمر عاجلاً،
I wouldn't have disturbed you.
ما كنت لأزعجك.
There's no time.
ليس هناك وقت.
(Shen Qingru.)
(شين تشينغرو.)
(Let's see how you explain this time.)
(دعنا نرى كيف ستشرح ذلك هذه المرة.)
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
She really is a shameless woman.
إنها حقاً امرأة عديمة الحياء.
Your...
لك...
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
How could it be you?
كيف يمكن أن تكون أنت؟
Don't come near.
لا تقترب.
Ru.
رو.
Little beauty.
جمال صغير.
Stay away!
ابتعدوا!
Don't come near!
لا تقترب!
If you dare touch her,
إذا تجرأت على لمسها،
I'll make sure you die without a trace.
سأضمن موتك دون أن تترك أثراً.
Ru.
رو.
Yuwen Que.
يوين كيو.
You ruined me completely.
لقد دمرتني تماماً.
Are you satisfied now?
هل أنت راضٍ الآن؟
Go ahead, laugh at me all you want.
تفضل، اضحك عليّ كما تشاء.
It's been three years.
لقد مرّت ثلاث سنوات.
Do you really hate me that much?
هل تكرهني حقاً إلى هذه الدرجة؟
Hate?
يكره؟
You destroyed my whole family, leaving us without a grave.
لقد دمرت عائلتي بأكملها، وتركتنا بلا قبر.
No single word of hate can fix this.
لا يمكن لكلمة كراهية واحدة أن تصلح هذا الوضع.
I wish you were dead.
أتمنى لو كنت ميتاً.
I've sent Heng Dao to investigate.
أرسلت هينغ داو للتحقيق.
Shut up.
اسكت.
You executioner.
أيها الجلاد.
Guards!
حراس!
Save...
يحفظ...
If you try to die,
إذا حاولت أن تموت،
I'll make everyone you care about die with you.
سأجعل كل من تهتم لأمرهم يموتون معك.
You dare?
أتجرؤ؟
We've known each other for years.
نعرف بعضنا البعض منذ سنوات.
You still don't know
ما زلت لا تعرف
that I mean what I say.
أعني ما أقول.
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
How could it be you?
كيف يمكن أن تكون أنت؟
You really think
هل تعتقد حقاً
I don't know your tricks?
لا أعرف حيلك؟
I don't know what you're talking about.
لا أعرف عما تتحدث.
You drugged her.
لقد قمت بتخديرها.
You had people ruin her reputation.
لقد تسبب أشخاص في تشويه سمعتها.
All of it,
كل ذلك،
you thought I didn't know?
هل ظننت أنني لا أعرف؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I...
أنا...
I only did it for you.
لم أفعل ذلك إلا من أجلك.
I just wanted to protect you, I...
أردت فقط حمايتك، أنا...
Cousin.
ابن عم.
I truly didn't mean it.
لم أقصد ذلك حقاً.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Before she passed, the Old Madam entrusted the princess to you.
قبل وفاتها، عهدت السيدة العجوز بالأميرة إليك.
She's your last family in this world.
إنها عائلتك الأخيرة في هذا العالم.
I searched for her
بحثت عنها
across mountains and rivers,
عبر الجبال والأنهار،
neglecting sleep and food.
إهمال النوم والطعام.
Finally, after so much effort...
وأخيراً، بعد كل هذا الجهد...
If I hear you speak one more word,
إذا سمعتك تنطق بكلمة أخرى،
I'll send you to meet your mother.
سأرسلك لمقابلة والدتك.
I didn't see anything.
لم أرَ شيئاً.
I didn't hear anything.
لم أسمع شيئاً.
Get out!
اخرج!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
I take my leave.
أستأذن بالانصراف.
(Yuwen Que.)
(يوين كيو.)
(You set up this prison for me.)
(لقد أنشأت هذا السجن لي.)
(But you didn't know I have my own spies inside.)
(لكنك لم تكن تعلم أن لدي جواسيس خاصين بي في الداخل.)
(Ji.)
(من الـ.)
(Wait for my signal.)
(انتظر إشارتي.)
(I must escape.)
(يجب أن أهرب.)
Shen Qingru.
شين تشينغرو.
You're getting bolder by the day.
تزداد جرأة يوماً بعد يوم.
In just a few days,
في غضون أيام قليلة فقط،
you dare come to me,
أتجرؤ على المجيء إليّ؟
to secretly meet in this dungeon.
للاجتماع سراً في هذه الزنزانة.
How many guards have you brought, Your Ladyship?
كم عدد الحراس الذين أحضرتهم يا سيدتي؟
Do you want to search me?
هل تريد البحث عني؟
You...
أنت...
Look.
ينظر.
I don't even have a hairpin on me.
ليس لدي حتى دبوس شعر.
Why be so guarded, Your Ladyship?
لماذا كل هذا الحذر يا سيدتي؟
Stop acting pitiful.
توقف عن التصرف بشفقة على النفس.
Wasn't the last lesson enough?
ألم يكن الدرس الأخير كافياً؟
Lesson?
درس؟
I know Your Ladyship
أعرف سيدتي
wants to kill me.
يريد قتلي.
But sadly...
لكن للأسف...
Sadly what?
للأسف ماذا؟
Sadly, you don't even have the courage to kill me.
للأسف، أنت لا تملك حتى الشجاعة لقتلي.
You dare humiliate me?
أتجرؤ على إذلالي؟
I'm just speaking the truth.
أنا فقط أقول الحقيقة.
You hate me, Your Ladyship.
أنتِ تكرهينني يا سيدتي.
But you fear him.
لكنك تخاف منه.
Caught between the two,
عالق بين الاثنين،
does it trouble you?
هل يزعجك ذلك؟
What exactly are you trying to say?
ما الذي تحاول قوله بالضبط؟
Your Ladyship.
سيدتي.
How about I help you come up with
ما رأيك أن أساعدك في التوصل إلى...
a solution that satisfies both sides?
حل يرضي الطرفين؟
What solution?
ما الحل؟
Help me deliver a message.
ساعدني في إيصال رسالة.
I promise
أعدك
I will disappear forever
سأختفي إلى الأبد
from both your lives.
من حياتكما معًا.
Deliver it to whom?
لمن يتم تسليمها؟
Su Changji.
سو تشانغجي.
This name should be familiar to Your Ladyship.
هذا الاسم يجب أن يكون مألوفاً لسيدتكم.
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
I'm just
أنا فقط
a fish on a chopping board, waiting to be cut.
سمكة على لوح تقطيع، في انتظار تقطيعها.
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
Rather than being slowly tortured to death by Yuwen Que,
بدلاً من أن يتعرض للتعذيب البطيء حتى الموت على يد يوين كيو،
I might as well go all in.
ربما من الأفضل أن أغامر بكل شيء.
Your Ladyship, I beg you.
سيدتي، أرجوكم.
Please help me this once.
أرجو مساعدتي هذه المرة.
I swear, if you help me,
أقسم بالله، إذا ساعدتني،
I will immediately leave the capital.
سأغادر العاصمة فوراً.
You and His Highness can be together in harmony.
يمكنك أنت وصاحب السمو أن تعيشا معاً في وئام.
Rare indeed,
نادر حقاً،
you also know how to yield.
أنت تعرف أيضاً كيف تتنازل.
I'm just
أنا فقط
tired.
مرهق.
Speak.
يتكلم.
What do you want me to deliver?
ماذا تريدني أن أوصل؟
Deliver this letter.
قم بتسليم هذه الرسالة.
(General's Residence)
(مقر إقامة الجنرال)
Commander.
قائد.
Please open the door.
يرجى فتح الباب.
It's already the third day, Commander.
لقد مر ثلاثة أيام بالفعل يا قائد.
I dare to...
أجرؤ على...
When the old general fell in battle,
عندما سقط الجنرال العجوز في المعركة،
you were never so despondent.
لم تكن يوماً بهذا القدر من اليأس.
Commander.
قائد.
(Do you want the military seal or your life?)
(هل تريد الحصول على الختم العسكري أم حياتك؟)
(Think carefully, General.)
(فكر جيداً يا جنرال.)
I give you three days, General.
أعطيك ثلاثة أيام يا جنرال.
Ancestors of the Su family above,
أسلاف عائلة سو المذكورة أعلاه،
this unfilial descendant is guilty.
هذا الوريث العاق مذنب.
(Spirit tablet of Tian Wuyuan) At age four,
(لوح روح تيان وويوان) في سن الرابعة،
(Spirit tablet of Li Lunjue) you taught me martial arts.
(لوح روح لي لونجوي) لقد علمتني فنون الدفاع عن النفس.
At age six,
في سن السادسة،
you taught me to hunt tigers.
لقد علمتني كيف أصطاد النمور.
(Spirit tablet of Nan)
(لوح روحي لنان)
At fourteen,
في الرابعة عشرة من عمره،
you brought me to the battlefield.
لقد أحضرتني إلى ساحة المعركة.
I know my guilt.
أعرف ذنبي.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
I seek no fame or achievement.
لا أسعى إلى الشهرة أو الإنجاز.
No desire to be recorded in history.
لا رغبة في أن يُسجل اسمي في التاريخ.
I only...
أنا فقط...
I only wish her safety.
كل ما أتمناه لها هو السلامة.
(Shen Qingru, Jinhua Hall)
(شين تشينغرو، قاعة جينهوا)
So it's you.
إذن أنت هو.
Qingru.
كينغرو.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
Madam. This is freshly made Poria cake from the kitchen.
سيدتي، هذه كعكة بوريا طازجة من المطبخ.
I specially brought it for you.
لقد أحضرتها خصيصاً لك.
You must try it.
يجب أن تجربها.
Much obliged.
ًشكراً جزيلا.
The cake is fresh out of the oven.
الكعكة طازجة من الفرن.
Best eaten warm.
يُفضل تناوله دافئاً.
You must try it.
يجب أن تجربها.
(Try to make His Highness unconscious. I'll meet at the east gate)
(حاولوا إفقاد سموه الوعي. سأقابلكم عند البوابة الشرقية)
(of Chengguang Hall at midnight. If successful,)
(من قاعة تشنغوانغ في منتصف الليل. إذا نجحت،)
(we can leave the capital in three days.)
(يمكننا مغادرة العاصمة في غضون ثلاثة أيام.)